Mohammed Sameer Syed

Student

About Me

An Undergrad in the department of ECE at the NIT Srinagar. In the past years I have gained experience in the field of ML/DL Artificial intelligence Ethical Hacking Android Development Python DSA Electronics and Communication systems.

Contact

- **U** +91 6005867210
- sdmohammedsameer@gmail.com
- Andhra Pradesh

Social Links

- https://github.com/SyedMohammedSameer
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohammed-sameer-syed-215a011b9

Skills

Mathematics

C

C++

Python

Java

Kotlin

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

NLP

Ethical Hacking

Android Development

Education

National Institute of Technology (NIT) Srinagar

2019 - Present

B.Tech-Electronics and Communication

Experience

Indian Institute of Technology, Indore-Research Intern

2022 - Present

Working on Space Weather Prediction using ML/AI.

1stopai-Artificial Intelligence Intern

2021 - Present

Working on projects of Handwritten Digit Classification Natural Language Processing.

Verzeo Info Tech-Machine Learning Intern

2021 - 2021

Learned basic regression and classification techniques in ML.

Project

Age calculating App

A Basic age calculating app that gives age as output when the DOB is entered.

Hand Written Digit Classification

An SVM based Machine Learning Model that predicts Handwritten Digits

Twitter News Bot

A Twitter Bot that Auto Retweets likes replies based on the trending tweets working as News Feed Bot.

Achievements

Received a LOR during the 30-Day Workshop on Artificial Intelligence conducted by MyCaptain.

Secured 4th position in Inter NIT-IIT IQ quiz conducted by Unacademy.

Runner-Up in IEEE Brainly Event.